

## Competences

- \*Critical thinking
- \*Problem solving.
- \*Teamwork and
- collaboration.
- \*Professionalism and strong work ethic. \*communications skills. \*Leadership.

## **Achievements**

### **ISO COURSE**

▼ ISO 9001 & ISO 14001 & ISO 45001

# Additional activities

- **†** Travel
- Adapting Animals
- kick boxing player

## Contact

### Contact

- ♠ Dubai, UAE
- **\** +971552127749
- nadaabdelrazik14@gmail.com
- **4** 07.07.1994
- coffee addict
- © +971552127749

### Social

in passant ahmedabdelrazik

## PASSANT **ABD ELRAZIK**

OPERATIONS MANAGER

### Profile

I am a flexible and experienced vessel operator with excellent time management skills. I am a good communicator with proven inter personal skills and am used to working in a team whilst also being capable of using own initiative. I am skilled In dealing with problems in a resourceful manner and negotiating to achieve beneficial agreement. I am always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges.

## Experience

**2023 - Present** 

### **SEAMASTER MARITIME CO.**

OPERATIONS MANAGER, DUBAI Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2021 - 2023

### **IBRAMAR SHIPPING CO.**

**OPERATIONS MANAGER** 

- \*involved in the analysis and monitoring of operational data to ensure potential problems are averted.
- \*also oversees the implementation of workflow improvements that may enhance customers' satisfaction, as well as optimise the use of the organisations resources.
- \* provide advice to ship crews and management on cargo requirements, tank cleaning, stability and stress and to maintain all statutory requirements for the ship in this field. \*also be required to analyse operational data to help improve inefficiencies and to predict
- help improve inefficiencies and to predict operational problems.
- \* good communicator and have good negotiation skills.
- \*strong problem solving and analytical skills and may be required to work irregular hours.
- \*participating with top mgt about company restricture.
- \* choosing and attending the interviews of operations & port teams
- \* reporting to top mgt about company situation and position
- \* revising and approved final da and all final invoices .

## Experience

**2019 - 2021** 

# ALBAHARIA SHIPPING CO. SENIOR VESSELS OPERATOR PORT CALLS VESSELS:

Prepare vessel position updates and then forward on

responsible for ensuring the vessel's voyage is performed efficiently and ensuring costs are kept to a minimum Arrange and manage any advance payments from charterers and final

settlements when the voyage is complete. Coordinate the day-to-day operational activities, liaising with any external agents and marine Technical Superintendents etc to ensure efficient commercial operation.

Liaises with Charterers and Owners with respect to vetting inspections in relation to ports to be visited

Prepare vsl prof. da during her port calls Send a daily update about eta/etb/etc/ets Coordinate with boarding agents all vessel's updates

Send a daily report about discharging/loading operation

Prepare SOf , Nor , Manifest , Mate's Reciept . LOI ,LOP and bills of lading

Arrange all the crew change procedures, OTB and etc .  $\,$ 

Following up al vessels provisions /requirement

Following up parcels delivery to vessels Prepare vsl's final da.

### **SUEZ CANAL VESSELS:**

Prepare Suez canal tolls and da following up reving transit prearrival does send daily transit schedule for vessel follow up arrival, entrance and clearance of transiting vessel and send reports revise suez canal invoices

## Experience

**2019 - 2021** 

### Albaharia shipping Co.

Senior vessels operator PORT CALLS VESSELS:

- Prepare vessel position updates and then forward on
- responsible for ensuring the vessel's voyage is performed efficiently and ensuring costs are kept to a minimum
- Arrange and manage any advance payments from charterers and final settlements when the voyage is complete.
- Coordinate the day-to-day operational activities, liaising with any external agents and marine Technical Superintendents etc to ensure efficient commercial operation.
- Liaises with Charterers and Owners with respect to vetting inspections in relation to ports to be visited
- Prepare vsl prof. da during her port calls
- Send a daily update about eta/etb/etc/ets
   Coordinate with boarding agents all vessel's updates
- Send a daily report about discharging/loading operation
- Prepare SOf , Nor , Manifest , Mate's Reciept . LOI ,LOP and bills of lading
- Arrange all the crew change procedures, OTB and etc .

Following up al vessels provisions /requirement

- Following up parcels delivery to vessels
- Prepare vsl's final da.

### **SUEZ CANAL VESSELS:**

- Prepare Suez canal tolls and da
- following up reving transit prearrival docs
- send daily transit schedule for vessel
- follow up arrival, entrance and clearance of transiting vessel and send reports
- revise suez canal invoices

## Experience

### 2017 - 2019

### NANMAR SHIPPING CO.

**VESSELS OPERATOR** 

Planning & coordination.

Daily planning and coordination of voyages, load & discharge operations and stowage plans. Checking bunkers requirement, cargo intakes, .respective voyage.

Port agencies and load- and discharge coordination.

Agents shall be nominated and appointed ensure daily follow-up on cargo operations and prospects.

Commercial coordination. Keeping

Customer's updated and tendering notices as per agreed terms.

Documentation. Ensure all required instructions pertaining to the cargo documents (e.g. Bills of Lading, Manifests, Mate's Receipts etc.) are made in due time.

Making SOf, Nor, Manifest, Mate's Reciept. LOI, LOP and bills of lading.

Sending all the required and daily Emails for ETA ETB ETC ETS.

Preparing all Pda and FDA.

Doing all the crew change procedures , OTB and etc.

### **2016 - 2017**

### NANMAR SHIPPING CO.

Martime accountant, city
Prepare vessel prof. da
Prepare shippers invoices for liner out
Prepare receivers invoices for
discharging/loading, hiring shore cranes, tally
and

weight co., and intermediation fees.
Following up all supplier invoices (tally co., stevedoring co. crew change arrangements agents, provisions agent and

arrangements agents, provisions agent and outside suppliers.)

Revise all Egyptian ports invoices for each voyage

.Prepare final da for all vessels calls

## Education

**2012** 

### **Bachelor Degree**

faculty of commerce, City bachelor in accounting dep. English section